[Music]
Hello, welcome to Amar Ujala The Bonus.
So first of all,
if you look at yesterday's market, after four days
of decline, the Indian market was seen making a
comeback on Tuesday.  Auspicious
situation was seen.  The June retail
inflation rate was lower than expected,
leading to a good rally and
investors' confidence returning due to the prospects of India-US trade agreements.  But
how sustainable is this boom?  This is a big question.
Because today's gift is Nifty, let me
show it to you on the screen once.  There is
pressure of about 100 points here.
So as soon as we
come, please flash Gift Nifty once
and after that you will see that
Gift Nifty is showing pressure of about 100 points here
and
weakness is being seen in the global market.
Especially,
this situation has been seen after the inflation numbers in America.  This
means that a make or break situation can be seen in the market today.   It
is very important to stay above 25,000.
We are continuously seeing a surge in mid-caps.
So,
according to experts, if the level of 25,000 remains
sustained then there
is hope of a rise.  This means that even if the market shows a dip, there
is a possibility of a pullback
here.  We will also understand that from Rajesh ji.
He will join us.  But
if the results of the companies and banking sector
disappoint, then the decline here may
increase.  So let
us now move on to
our next segment
here, which is called World at Fingertips, to understand this session in detail and to understand the developments around the world.
[Music]
So joining us from Mumbai is The Bonus
Creditor, Anshuman Tiwari Sir.
You are most welcome.
Thanks Harsh welcome to the world on fingers.
America's indirect entry into the war between Russia and Ukraine seems possible.
Meanwhile, conflict has started again in West Asia.
Trump has announced new tariffs
and
bond yields have risen in many markets around the world.  Stock, currency
and commodity markets will be affected by these events today
and it is going to be a confusing day for the stock markets.
Let us know in
detail which are the events that will
affect the Indian markets and the markets of the entire world today.  Donald Trump
said this morning that
tariffs of up to 200% could be imposed on pharmaceutical companies.
He said this in a conversation with Bloomberg and it can come into effect from August 1.
This is certainly very worrying
news for Indian pharma companies as Donald Trump has now
come close to the tariff rates he talked about
and has talked about tariffs of up to 200 percent.
However, Donald Trump has
also expressed the possibility of a trade agreement with India.
But some concrete signs or some
concrete structure does not seem to be emerging yet.
As the uncertainty and deadlock that has persisted
continues.  Trump has
announced a multi-billion dollar trade deal with Indonesia.  There is
no clarity about this either, but indications are that
Indonesia may be hit with a tariff of 19 to 20%.
Indonesia will purchase Boeing aircraft and
America will get greater access to the Indonesian market in agriculture and energy.  This
means Indonesia will open its market to
American agricultural products and
energy, especially oil and gas.
This is an important deal and
you can assume that if it is agreed upon
and Indonesia agrees to it, then
this will be the second important deal in Asia
which is likely to be officially announced
after Vietnam.
America has indicated that it will impose tariffs of 10% or more on 100 small countries with which
it has a trade deficit and with
whom it has bilateral trade.  This
means that Donald Trump is
slowly moving towards the August 1 deadline and
where he is now finalizing the entire tariff structure.
In these tariffs, special attention will be given to
Africa and Caribbean countries in pharma
and also on pharma and chips imports.
So now this tariff structure
seems to be almost clear.  The
situation in India remains uncertain.
Challenging news for India and the Indian markets came from NATO yesterday.  NATO
issued a very stern warning.  A big two-pronged
warning was issued that if
India and China in particular continue to trade with Russia, they
could face secondary sanctions.
America has already said that through one of its bills, it will
ban the import of oil and other goods from Russia to India and China.  There is a
challenge for India's oil imports.
Although its impact is not
visible on the oil market, its impact will definitely be visible
on the Indian economy and Indian oil imports.
Beyond the world of tariffs,
developments on the Russia-Ukraine front are rapidly unfolding, with
several incidents in the last 24 hours having
repercussions that will be felt in the near future.
Donald Trump has threatened to stop the war in 50 days.
He also
said that he plans to
provide Patriot missiles and other weapons to Ukraine through NATO.
He also hinted at this plan and
threatened to impose tariffs on countries trading with Russia.
I had said the same thing in the beginning
that now America is indirectly entering this war.
Donald Trump is
fed up with trying to negotiate peace with Putin,
and that frustration is
clearly visible in his statements and interviews.
European ministers have also
supported the plan to provide US weapons to Ukraine.
And however many weapons will be
available, how will the funding be done, how will the supplies be made
?  Its details are not clear yet.
But Europe has stood with America in this matter.
Germany and neighboring countries UK and
Canada are preparing to build a new pipeline to send weapons to Ukraine.
In which
America will also be involved and
weapons will be supplied to Ukraine rapidly.   The
Noklas countries and Germany
also face a significant threat from Ukraine's expansion plans
and hence these countries are very concerned about Russia's
plans.  Meanwhile,
Ukrainian President Zheltsky has
announced a government reshuffle.
Sweden's name has been proposed as Prime Minister.
This is also an important development
that will impact world politics in the midst of the Russia-Ukraine war.
Here
Putin's reaction has come.  Putin
is extremely aggressive.  He called Trump's 50-day
ceasefire ultimatum a mere drama
and said he would continue to
occupy large parts of Ukraine.
Their
program, plan and strategy to capture a large part of Ukraine remains fully intact.
Kamalin has also said that he is
not afraid of America's plan to send weapons.  But this threatens to escalate conflict in Europe.
Meanwhile, Russia has
hinted at a deeper alliance with China and India,
saying that if secondary sanctions are
imposed, a joint strategy will be developed to meet them.
Tensions are rising again in West Asia.
We will see its impact on oil prices.
Israel has attacked Syrian government
targets and has
warned of further attacks on our military bases
and now after Israel, Syria is on Israel's
target.  This appears to
increase the risk of security instability across the region.
These were the global diplomatic
news which will have indirect impact
on the market.  Now let us
go straight to the middle world of the economy and see
what are the big economic news
coming from different countries around the world.
Inflation has risen for the second time in the US,
and although the core CPI is lower than expected, the
Federal Reserve has signaled from the beginning
that tariff decisions are
likely to increase inflation.  Those signals are
confirmed by this inflationary increase
and the burst has been said to be a matter of concern.
With this, there is a possibility of some reduction in the pressure on Zero Power from Donald Trump to reduce interest rates in America.  It is
believed so.  However,
despite the inflation figures, Donald Trump is maintaining pressure.  In
fact, there are reports
that the search for a successor has begun.
Zero power 10-year bond deal in America is
at its highest.  I
told you in the beginning that bond yields have suddenly increased in many countries.
Concerns about budgets are growing.
Weaknesses in the economy due to widening trade deficits are making
borrowing
programmes more likely by governments.   The
10-year-old in the US is
at a four-week peak of the 10-year-old.  The 10-
year bond in Canada is at a 12-month high.
Manufacturing sales in Canada are
at a three-year low.  There has been chaos in Japan's bond
market since yesterday.  The
financial condition of the country is in danger.  The yield on the 10-year bond
is at its highest level since 2008 and the yield on the 30-year bond is
also at a record high.  Japan's
economy and the trend of Japan's bond
market will affect the markets of Asia and America today.   Meanwhile,
due to US sanctions, Chinese companies are
accelerating the purchase of AI chips from Nvidia
in light of the August 1 ban and Nvidia has
also started selling its chips.  China has
begun reassessing its risks amid Trump's trade threats and tariffs.  The whole world is
watching what new strategy China is coming up with for its trade.
Moving to the commodity market, Brent crude
prices are showing a decline.  There is weak demand.  There
is tariff stress.  However, the sanctions on Russia will
affect the
supply of crude oil in the international market.  The events in Syria
also have an impact.  But at present,
considering the supply of crude oil in the market, there is pressure on prices.
However, Golden State
gave its oil forecast yesterday, in which it
predicted a slight rise in Brent
and set a target price of $6.  The
target price of a barrel has been kept at Rs 66 and it is
believed that there may be a slight shortage in the market in the next half.
Therefore, Brent
prices will remain slightly stronger.  Meanwhile, oil
exporting countries are trying to understand the trade between Russia and the Middle East
in the light of the new sanctions
because the Middle
East countries also have a big trade with Russia.
Investment in gold has increased to protect against inflation.  Both gold and silver
are strong.
Newcastle coal futures have
hit a five-month high after a long period of trading on rising Chinese demand.
After a long time, we are seeing a rise in coal prices
and the reason for this is the
demand from China.  There is a slight deterioration in the steel.
We are seeing a rise in soybean and wheat.
This is a very important week in the world of crypto.  There's
a
Crypto Week in Washington, legislatively.  The
Stable Coin Act in the US House is being called the Genius Act.
Preparations for the vote on that have been going on for weeks.  The
Clarity Act is also on the agenda
which provides for market regulation of the
crypto market.  However, the dilemma is
who will regulate the crypto market in America?  The Securities Exchange
Commission, which regulates stock markets and financial
markets, similar to India's
SEBI or the commodity regulator, will
bring crypto under its purview.   It is
believed that this bill is likely to be passed by the US House.
But there could be
some confusion in the Senate.  It may get stuck.
But for now, this week could be a week of crypto
news in the US markets
and several major legal measures from the US.
And we will see its impact
on crypto laws in other countries as well.
Another important news from the
crypto market is coming from the US.   A
few weeks ago, a month ago, the Trump administration had
allowed Bitcoin to be accepted as collateral,
and home lending companies were asked to
accept Bitcoin as collateral.  Following this, there are indications
that pilots of Bitcoin mortgages are about to begin in some states.
This
is likely to increase the demand for Bitcoin.
Spain's BB Bank has
expanded into retail crypto services, and
banks in Europe are now slowly moving towards crypto and
digital
transactions, especially crypto
transactions.  There is
considerable turmoil in the currency market due to
turmoil in global fund markets and the
impact of inflation figures and tariffs in the US.  The dollar index is showing slight strength.
After a long time,
we saw some strength in the dollar index yesterday.  Reached 98.4.
We are seeing some safe haven demand due to US inflation and the impact of tariffs.
However, we will see bond yield pressure
on the dollar again in the coming times.  The
Japanese currency is at a nine-week low.
We have told you the condition of Japan's economy.  There
is pressure on the bond market.   There is an
impact of slowdown in the economy.   The
Indian rupee is stable.  RBI is monitoring the fund flow.  The
Russian ruble made a surprise move yesterday amid news of sanctions.
at its highest level in two years.  On one hand there
are sanctions and on the other hand the Russian ruble
is looking strong and the reason for this is that the
Central Bank of Russia has tightened its monetary
policy considerably.  It has been made quite strict.
Due to which we are seeing strength in the Russian currency.
Some prominent figures came to India.
Harsh mentioned to you about the inflation figures which
came yesterday and in both the inflation figures there was a
sharp decline in inflation, in fact
WPI
went into a state of outright deflation, for which there are many
interpretations in the market regarding demand, whether it is a
sign of demand decreasing or increasing, but
another figure came in India yesterday, the unemployment rate of India in June
came which is at 5.6%, the
unemployment rate among urban youth has reached 18.8%.  It
is a huge increase.  It was
17.9s in May.
There is a slight increase in the unemployment rate among rural youth also.
Here the indications are that the Prime Minister's Office has
approved the initial agenda of reform to change the entire structure of GST.
We have been telling you
in different programs in Bonus Point that Home
Minister Amit Shah has taken the responsibility of consensus among the states
and now the
next meeting of the GST Council is being awaited.
Where discussion on new rate fitment and new
slabs will begin.  In which one
slab is likely to be a 12th century slab.  The
biggest dilemma is
which products should be put in the 8s slab
and which should be placed in the higher slabs.
So now the real struggle in GST is beginning
which
we will see between the states and the Centre in the coming one and a half months.  The
proposal to increase the limit of foreign investment in public sector banks was already pending but has been deferred.  The
Reserve Bank
is currently studying this proposal.  Adani Group has made a
clean sweep for the assets of JP Group of India and now the matter has become a
bit interesting and complicated.  This
clean bid means that Adani Group did
not impose any conditions for the purchase.   The
matter is stuck on business terms.  Other
bids are also high.  But in all of them,
conditions of legal settlement,
conditions of removing legal hurdles, all these conditions have been imposed.
Now Bhayankar is in a dilemma whether to
go with the conditions or with the bid of Adani Group,
this will be watched today and the
reaction in the stock market will also be seen.
Another big news that came yesterday in ML is that the
government telecom company which
provides services in two metropolitan cities is sick and has limited
service, it has defaulted on loans worth Rs 8584 crore from seven banks.
This bank
is PNB.  It is a State Bank.  It is UCO Bank.  Indian
Overseas Bank.  There is Punjab and Sindh Bank
and there is Bank of India.  The
impact of this default will be visible on the market today.
New sanctions are being prepared on Russia in the next 24 hours.
We will see the impact of the warning given by NATO.  There
is a possibility of some reaction from India.  In the talks between China and India,
clarity was shown yesterday from the Indian side.
What is the response from China?  Does India
get some leniency in the supply of railway funds?  Everyone's eyes will be on this after Indian Foreign Minister Jaishankar's
visit to Beijing.  Is
China being a little generous
?  There is stability in the bond and commodity markets.
Especially we will see the impact of the global bond market
on the international markets.
Inflation figures will be released in the UK,
which will be closely watched as the UK
economy is also under pressure, and
industrial production figures are expected to be released in the US.
Meanwhile, it is the season of company results.  It
is the season in India.  The Indian
stock market will react to these results based on the
results of specific companies.  That's all for today
in the world on your fingers. From Mumbai, we
go back to Harsh in Noida.
Thank you very much Sir
for analyzing all the news in detail Sir.
[Music]
[Applause]
See, now we would have told you since when the
gap up of 100 points and 90 points is
clearly visible in Gift Nifty.  The
companies that are there today are Tech Mahindra, ITC,
Hotel LNT Technology Services, Angel 1.
Apart from this, tomorrow the
results of FI 25 for the fourth quarter of the financial year will come, there are DB Corp, there are many
Lotus Chocolates, there is a Reliance company here and there are
many other companies as well, the
numbers of Reliance Industrial Infrastructure will
come here, so there are many such numbers on
which you should keep an eye
and we will keep updating you continuously,
if you talk about the FI figures
here, then yesterday
if you look at the FI figures in the cash market, then
buying was seen here and whether we talk about index
futures or index
options, selling in index futures,
see this in front of you, FI has
made a purchase of Rs 120 crore and
along with this, DI has also been seen making a purchase of around Rs 1500 crore.  Whether we
talk about index futures or index
options, here you can
see that selling worth approximately Rs 153 crore has been seen
in index futures.
And talking about index options, he was
seen buying for Rs 4337 crore.   If we
talk about stock futures in options,
buying worth Rs 170 crore and
selling worth Rs 133 crore has been seen in stock options.
Apart from this, we will tell you what the option data says
because tomorrow is the
expiry and we are standing here exactly in the mid-session.
So let us show you the data of the option
here.  So you
see this because yesterday was the expiry
of Sussex on Tuesday and tomorrow here on Thursday is the
expiry of Nifty and you see,
we are in the middle here at 25200, you call
writers, you will see the maximum
open interest here, after that at 25300
25400, here a gathering of 84 lakh shares, 85 lakh
shares is seen here.
Apart from this, look at the position of put writers,
here at 25200 there is an
open interest of around 89 lakhs, after that at 2500 and
then at 25000 there are shares worth more than 1 crore
here, the open interest here
means what happened, support seems to be forming at 25000
and the resistance here is of
25200, although now we will
understand everything in detail from Rajesh ji, but
what is the situation being seen in the global market, let me
tell you that yesterday the NSD was seen
reaching a record high,
a tremendous situation was seen in NVDR
and the numbers that came from America,
ah consumer, basically the inflation
figures here created pressure, here the futures are still
showing negative, here the
NSD was seen positive yesterday, but
pressure was seen in SNP 500 as well,
talk about Asian markets, whether it is Shanghai or NI,
pressure is being seen on everything,
look at the whole, if you talk about FTSE,
pressure is being seen in the European market as well here  But
this is the situation that is being seen, now we
go to
Rajesh Bansal ji, the amazing director of Mid Funsaf, to analyze the market in detail. Sir,
you are most welcome,
hello sir.
Greeting sir.  Sir, my first question is that please
tell our viewers
what should we consider the reason for yesterday's rise, sir?  Because inflation
figures also came.  Such a situation was also
seen that the trade deal between India and America may be
seen cooling off.  Meaning, what should be
considered the reason why the
market was seen to be rising?
No, nothing like that Harsh ji.  Yes,
within four to five days, Nifty had
fallen by almost 600 points.  There was a
sharp decline in four days.
Like we talked about the statistics regarding trade policy,
if there is no positive news then there is no
negative news either.  Till now
Mr. Trump has not imposed any major tariff on India.
Like it has been imposed on many countries.
So this no negative
result is also a positive news and
such a thing is still expected.  Nothing like this is going to happen anytime soon.
Human results have
not been that bad.  The market did
not have much expectations from him.  So we are
coming in the same line and the
market was oversold for quite some time and there were technically
positive divergences also.  We also thought that
Nifty would go up to 25,000-150 and Nifty
went a little higher.  The market surprises every time.
Absolutely sir.  So today, Sir Gift Nifty is
showing a decline of approximately 90 points.  The pressure is showing here.
How do you think one should trade in today's market
?  What kind of
strategy should be made?  Harsh ji, it seems that the
market has found a strong support of Rs 25,000
and the market is
not going to break it easily now.  So with this support the
market will once again try to go up
but until the market does not close negativey above 25270
further ups will not be seen,
so the market can move between 25000 and 25270 for a
day and after that it will take a further
direction,
okay sir, this is today's strategy, how to make it, sir,
today as you also told, the market is opening gap down
because yesterday Nifi closed at 25195 and right now
if Singapore Nifi or Gift Nifi is
any indication then the market is opening 80 to 90 points
down.
Yes, when the
market opens down, the first support comes at 2575
and between that 2520 and 50, so we
thought that we will buy in the market between 2550 to 75.   We
will place a stop loss of 24980 as the market will
now remain bearish below 24,980.  The
market does not become bearish before that.  So
buy in the range of 2550 to 2575.
Place a stop loss at 24,980 and the intraday
market can again move towards 25,225.  It is
possible that the market may again move around yesterday's high.
Ok sir.  So here you told
that if you want to adopt today's strategy then
you should buy in Nifi in the range of 25,50 to 25,75.
Keep the stop loss below 24,980.  And Sir also said that
unless the market goes below 24,980,
you should not look at it as a bearish mood.   The
targets given for intraday
show the possibility of a rise to 25,225
here and Sir, meaning bearish,
we will believe it only when the situation reaches 24,980.
Yes, if the market
closes below that level any day,
or if it trades below it for half an hour, at
least for an hour, then the market will
open at lower levels, which can go up to 24750, whether that
possibility will come or not, we will
see, the market was not allowing me to see it below that, right now
we are
saying it again and again that it is a
good thing for the investor and the second good thing that can happen is
Harsh ji, if the market closes above 25270
today, then the
market will become a little bullish and the
market will want to go a little higher.
Ok sir.  Thank you so much sir.  You can
join us and share all the information.
Okay, hello.
Greeting sir.
And meanwhile, questions are continuously coming for all the viewers.  A
very warm welcome to all the
viewers and in the meantime Pankaj
Randed ji has joined us who is the founder
of Inx Research Advisories.  Sir,
you are very welcome.
Thank you Harsh ji.  Thank you very much for
inviting me.
Same here sir.  Ah, my first question sir, a
decline was seen in the last four days.  The
pressure was palpable.  Yesterday the
situation seemed to be improving.
But right now, here on Gift Nifty,
pressure of around 90 to 100 points is being seen.  So will this
create pressure in the market or
can it also see a pullback?
Yes, good morning Harsh.  Good morning
everyone.  As far as we talk about Nifty,
if we look at it from a technical perspective, then
I feel that yesterday was a day that somewhere or the other it is
trying to show the reliability market.
Look at this bounce back as a reflection,
definitely the conviction of put writers at 25100 and 25000
is very strong.  Ah, we saw good additions within the put writers
at 25100 and above the 25,000 level.
If
we talk about figures, then
around 187000 contracts have been added for put writers
and
if we look at 2500, then around 37 lakh
new contracts have been seen being introduced there.
I think there is a level of 25,000 which is
quite decisive.  But I'd like to
go into the range a little bit.  Ah 2550 to 25100
and that is the strongest support.  Ah, let's see
when the market goes below 25,950 to 25,980.
Overall, Trump's factor has also become a big factor in the
way tariffs are being
talked about.  There
is no clarity on us yet.  But still I am
watching some news coming.  So Trump has
said that the tariff on pharma can come by the end of this month
and tariffs of around 200% can be
imposed here for 12 to 18 months.
So this will be a
bit negative news for pharma.  Just
I think it must have been hardly 30 to 40
seconds.  This news has just been pumped
here.  Sir, actually it was that 10 to 15 days
ago, one and a half to two weeks ago, exactly the
same statement had come from Don Trump that
we will invest 200% on pharma and it will take one
to one and a half years, sir, after that there was a
slight slowdown in the market, then again the
pharma sector was seen gaining momentum,
today's statement
I feel is a bit
prominent
and along with that we cannot ignore the results as well, the kind
of results that are expected today
in heavyweights like Jeel Deltas and Tata C
Chemicals and this can
define the mood and environment of the market a little bit.  But the
Trump factor is already a factor.  The
market has already reacted to it.  The
anticipation was good
in the market but the last two-three sessions have been a bit
tough for us.  But stock
specific actions can definitely be seen.  A
continuous decline has been seen in Nifty IT.
So somewhere now it seems that the
market will
show some responsiveness.
Relevance will show.  Sir, according to you, which
pick could be today?  Which stocks
should one look at?
Yes, I think I think
buying should be recommended on delivery.  The
delivery stock here is
currently trading at around 415 416 in its futures.
So its stop loss should be
₹405 with a stop loss of ₹46,
a good play can be made
for the level of ₹430 up to ₹435.
Ok sir.  So you told about delivery, the
situation is being seen in futures at the price of 415.
Here you
can place bets for price 430 to price 435 here.
But don't forget to place a stop loss.
You have to see this status of 405.
This thing has to be taken care of by placing a stop loss.  Meanwhile,
Sumitra Patel ji is sending it here.
Good Morning.  Hemant Dugg ji is saying
good morning.  Hey Hemant ji, you
send questions on Sapphire Food every day.  Please
send us some more questions,
we will definitely incorporate your questions.
Arjun Gupta ji good morning.
And here Pandurang ji is saying that I
love the bonus.  Many thanks to all the
viewers.  The way you
show your love.  Sir, let us take a question from Ajay ji.  I
want to know your view on Netco Pharma because the news about the pharma has already
come out, so
what would be your advice regarding Netco Pharma?
Yes
and apart from this, Rahul
structural structural is looking quite good.  The kind of
boom that we witnessed here yesterday at Natco Pharma.
If we look at yesterday's low, then from 970 this
stock is rising to 108 1020, which means
you can understand that we have seen a rise of up to 5%.
In yesterday's session, it was seen trading with a
very good volume even on the daily time frame,
but definitely it is approaching 200 DEMA
somewhere.  Conditional
trade will be above 1020,
if it crosses the cash levels then we will buy.  At
present, we would like to wait for eight to nine points
here.
Ok sir.  Sir, let us also take a question from Rahul
Dixit ji.
He has bought 500 shares of Aditya Birla Capital at the
price of Rs 275.  Currently trading around 271.  There was a
good rally throughout the month
but the stock has seen strong pressure in the last one week.
Sir, please tell me the name of the stock.
Sir Aitya Birla Capital AB Capital
ji, look at a rising,
we can see a pattern of a rising wedge in it.
Coming forward here, there is
a flag of a little down slow.
Approached from around the 20 day mark.  I
think there should not be a big decline in it.
260 265 would be a good
range.  We
can make additions there.  I think
this stock can do very well.   It does
n't take long to reach levels 288 and 300.  The undertone I have on this is
bullish.  I would like to
add this in case of any decline here.   It
is advisable to add it in any decline.  Here we take a question from a prince.
Sir regarding Garden Reach Shipbuilders.
He has bought around 50 shares
at the price of Rs 3100.  Right now this stock is trading around 2672,
sir, and we are continuously
observing that some of the shipbuilding
stocks are specifically
witnessing a decline.  Sir, it has fallen by more than 9%
in the last five days and many
types of reports are also coming which are showing ship
building related stocks
as a pressure in the coming days.
This kind of situation is being seen regarding his earnings till FI 29.
How are you viewing Garden Ech Ship Builders
?  Look, the entire defence space has been
witnessing a continuous decline for the last few sessions and look, this
sector, somewhere or the other, I
would definitely like to say that it had
increased beyond limits even in terms of valuation.
So it was natural that a small pen would come inside it.
I think that
stocks like Garden Shipyard are pretty high
beta counters.  Meaning, when they break, they
break in a very powerful way
and when they grow, they grow in the same powerful
way.  But
I think the buying range should be within this, the
buying range should be within 2510 2520.
From here onwards, we may see a
little more decline.  But there is
no need to panic.
Add a little bit at the lower level and
stay in the trading zone, then you
can see good trading moves.
If you are a long term investor then definitely
hold it.  The situation may be
seen improving in the
future.
Ok sir.  First of all, Sir, let us discuss stocks.
This yielded results.  Let us
talk about SDB Financial Services.
Tomorrow is the results and it is the first time the company has
reported results since its IPO.   If we
talk about net profit here, there has been a
downfall of about
2.4% here because the earlier
figure was Rs 582 crores, from there it has
come down to around Rs 568 crores.
On the revenue front, Sir has seen a growth of 15%.  A
surge has been observed.
If we look at the net interest here, there
is an increase of 18% there too.  If we talk about net interest margin here,
this situation is visible here also.  Gross
NPA, if we say here, has increased from approximately
2.26% to
2.56%.  There has been a slight
increase in gross NPA.
And here in the credit cost, an
increase of about 62% has been seen here also.
But Sir, there is
pressure on the profit and net profit.
Clearly as you can see here the
revenue has increased but the profit has decreased.
Look sir, I
always give my opinion more on technicals than fundamentals.
Yes,
but these events are quarterly
events, so this also
cannot be ignored.  Somewhere or the other, the net
profit seems to be getting dragged down.  The
biggest worrying factor is that
NPA has increased significantly
here.  So that's a bit of a concern.
This is the NBFC stock that has been in the news recently.  If we
talk about data, then even on the daily time frame,
very large data is not visible.
But in the shorter time frame,
I think its base is
around the level of 428 to 430.  Ah,
if it closes
below 428 or 828 on the daily time frame, then it will
definitely be necessary to take a position above it.
And at the higher level, I think
if it crosses above 850, above 200 Dema,
above the shorter time frame, then the
level of 850-55
is visible here on 30 minutes and above 60 minutes.  If it
follows the levels on the charts, then it
is a sign of consolidation.  Another
scenario would be that below 828, it may
see a fall and above 855,
continuous buying
interest may be seen in it.
So sir, because many investors
consider it as a long term bet.
According to you, those who have
got allotment from IPO should
remain here.
Yes, I definitely have seen this as the biggest IPO in this space was seen being
introduced here in the biggest market.
Backed by HDFC Bank.  But
if we look at the technology, it
is completely different from HDFC.  If
we look at their business plans, they are
completely different from HDFC.  Meaning,
if we look at it overall, there is no connection between HDFC and HDB.
Right from the technology
to the business perspective,
both of them are very different.  But definitely the
subsidiary is a very big entity.   It would be
advisable to hold.  Prices ranging from ₹1050 to ₹160 can be
seen here.  And I am
saying out of the box that those
people who I actually do not pay
much attention to IPOs.  But to all
those who consulted me, I would always
say that they should always remain
long-term
investors in such IPOs.  So, you may see a lot of money in the coming time.
But
it also gave an opening gain of 13-14%.
So many people also leave from there.   Left.
Absolutely fine.  Sir, you have
told here that targets up to Rs 1000 can also be
seen here.  Sir, here
is a question from Khusgara Dwivedi ji.  They are saying
sir, you can enter Jio Finance.  Are the
current levels okay
or should we wait a bit?  Let's
see when these results come.
Look Harsh ji, I have already expressed my opinion on this on many different channels.
I believe that if this is your view of four to five years then it would be
advisable to hold it.  This is quite big, meaning it can
prove to be a multibagger.  The way
it fell now, the reason was quite clear
that the
IPO of Jio Platforms was not
introduced within 2025 and on the same day, I think it was
last Thursday.  It was last
week's Thursday that we saw
a slight decline on the same day
and the stock is continuously
giving good performance.
It is coming through the level of 200 to the level of 320-325.
Of course keep it.  Any dip within it should be
a buying opportunity here and
stay in it for a very long period.
If it performs in four digits in the
future, then it will
not be a surprise, sir.
Ok.  So sir, purchases can be made at the current levels,
right?   You
can definitely buy here as well
and if this stock comes at any lower level then
definitely buying advice will be given in this too.
Okay sir, I would like a short, very small answer from
you.  Anas ji's question is, Sir,
he has purchased Signity India at the price of Rs 41.  What should be done now
?
Saty sir.   Yes
sir.  Security India Sir.
Yes, see, this stock was in very strong momentum.
If we look at the sessions of the last three-four days and yesterday and the day before yesterday, we can see
a Doji formation
here.
The stock is seen continuously moving down by forming a base of the upper range around 45-46.
So somewhere or the other, a pressure
point, a good supply zone is
visible here from 46.  And
if we look at the upper level, then ah
46.90 means 46 and 47, these two clusters are such
that a good amount of supply is
seen being generated here.  But the positive
thing here is that it is trading above VVP.
Trying to give a breakout of the trending line.  Good
volumes are being seen here.
Money can be made within swing trades.
If you hold it positionally, then
I would like to tell
you that you should maintain a stop loss of ₹42 from here
and
hold it.  When it goes above 46-47
then further averaging has to be done within it.  Meaning,
if the market is trending and if the
market moves in the way we are anticipating, then it would be
advisable to average at the higher level.
Within the gradual target, you can see ₹55.  As a
disclaimer,
I have shared this stock
with my clients.
Ok sir.  Thank you so much sir.  You
joined us and shared all the information
sir.   Thank
you.  Thank you very much.   It
's the same sir.  So how did you like today's show?   Don't miss it.
You must tell us.
We will tell you what shows are on throughout the day.
Watch from 10:00 am to
11:30 am as Pradeep Hadar joins us as CEO PSG
Capital.  Apart from this,
Pankaj Rand ji will join us again from 10 to 10:30.  He is the
founder of Inx Research
Advisors.  Apart from this, from 11 to 11:30
VLA Ambala ji will join Stock Market
Today, who is SEBI registered and at 1:00 pm
Dr. Ravi Singh is going to join here,
questions of Senior VP Railgate Retail Research
in Lakh Taka and at 4:00 pm, do not
forget to watch the question related to mutual funds,
you can ask questions related to mutual funds in this.
So let me excuse you for now.
Many viewers are
left with questions.  So we apologize to you for that.
But you must join by 8:30.
Connect quickly so we
can incorporate your questions.  Some
viewers have just joined, so you should
start joining a little early.
Thank you.
[Music]
Om